The NestedModule section (aka Nest, NestedModules, or Nested) is a hashtable containing the names of modules to nest and the directories in which they will be placed.

Each value can be:
* A : followed by a list of schematics (separated by comma)
* A name of a module followed by a list of schematics (separated by a comma)
* The name of a module

This example nests the module Start-Scripting in the subdirectory Blog

    @{
        NestedModules = @{
            "Blog" = "Start-Scripting:Blog"
        }
    }
