# Get-Web is a wonderfully flexible command.  It helps you slice and dice web services and web data into new techology.
# One of the simplest, and most powerful, capbilities of Get-Web is to get all of the tags from a document.   For instance, this one liner will grab all of the anchor tags from [start-automating.com](http://start-automating.com).

Get-Web -Tag 'a' -Url http://start-automating.com/

# It's also simple to get general site metadata.

Get-Web -MetaData -Url http://start-automating.com/

# You can also extract out HTML5 Microdata from a page.  For instance, this one-liner gets everything that IMDB knows about the first movie in it's database.

Get-Web -Url "http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0000001/" -AsMicrodata -ItemType http://Schema.org/Movie


# This one liner helps me make dinner.  

Get-Web -Url "http://www.myrecipes.com/recipe/veal-and-artichoke-stew-with-avgolemono-10000000226585/" -AsMicrodata -ItemType http://data-vocabulary.org/Recipe




# You can also query openGraph.

# [OpenGraph](http://developers.facebook.com/docs/reference/api/) is an interesting technology from Facebook that documents objects and their relationships.

# It turns all of Facebook via a gigantic RESTful JSON web service.

# To interact with this with Powershell Pipeworks, simply use the -AsJson parameter from [Get-Web](http://powershellpipeworks.com/Get-Web-?)

# This example gets information about Powershell Pipeworks.



Get-Web -Url "https://graph.facebook.com/250363831747570" -AsJson

<#
OpenGraph information can also be embedded within a web page, and extracted directly from that page.


If a page has OpenGraph data, it often contains a helpful name, image, description.


This example also shows using the -UseWebRequest parameter, which will use a simple HttpWebRequest object to communicate.  By default, Get-Web will try to download things with the xmlHTTP object, which is faster and can impersonate a logon within Internet Explorer.  
#>


Get-Web -Url "http://imdb.com/" -OpenGraph -UseWebRequest 


<#
You can use the -Parameter parameter to call a web service.  For instance, this sort script uses Get-Web to call Write-ScriptHTML remotely
#>

Get-Web -Url "http://powershellpipeworks.com/Write-ScriptHtml/" -Parameter @{
    "Write-ScriptHTML_Text" = "function Get-Foo() {
    <#
    .Synopsis
        A Sample Script
    .Description
        A Sample Description
    #>
}"
} -UseWebRequest -Method Post

