Another important reason why to use PowerShell Pipeworks is the degree to which it can let you have an integrated intranet.   


Since most web languages come from a linux background, making them work with windows is often like trying to fit a round peg into a square hole.  



Most enterprise IT applications need to do things like work with Active Directory, Exchange, or Sharepoint - Technologies PowerShell already works well with.  
You can use the -AsIntranetSite parameter on ConvertTo-ModuleService along with -AppPoolCredential to make any module available on your intranet as a certain user.            



PowerShell Pipeworks also includes a useful function to look up information from Active Directory:  Get-Person.  
 
