# CRUD is a standard set of operations that most web applications need to perform.
# It stands for:
# Create, Read, Update, and Delete
# Rather than make you write all of the CRUD yourself, you can create a simple set of CRUD commands with the Pipeworks function Write-Crud.

# The simplest way to create a CRUD system with Write-Crud is to use schemas.  For instance, this creates the CRUD system for a blog:
Write-Crud -Table My -Partition Blog -Schema http://schema.org/BlogPosting 

# Another site that lists schemas is shouldbeonschema.org
Write-Crud -Table My -Partition FAQ -Schema http://shouldbeonschema.org/FAQ

# If you don't find the schema you like on schema.org, you can define a custom CRUD system
Write-CRUD -Table My -Partition CustomItem -TypeName MyCustomCrud -Field @{
    'Name' = 'The Name of the Item'
    'Description' = 'The description of the item'            
}


 
