Windows may have many possiblilties, but it's only within the past decade that it's been plausible to superglue them together.  Most scripting languages are not focused on OS integration as much as text manipulation.  Because of PowerShell's heavy emphasis on objects and Windows' wide world of classes, PowerShell is able to interact with many more components out of the box than any other scripting language on earth.  This is why writing PowerShell is sometimes called "Scripting with Superglue".  PowerShell Pipeworks enables you to glue together all of the things you can work with in PowerShell, and use them in a web application.  



Out of the box, PowerShell works wonderfully with:


* Anything from .NET
* Almost all COM Objects
* Anything from WMI
* Any .exe
* Any SOAP Web service (with New-WebServiceProxy)
* Any REST web service (with System.Net.Webclient)
* Low-Level windows Operations (via P/Invoke)



And if this wasn't enough, you can use the built in PowerShell cmdlet Add-Type to compile your way there.
 
