# SecureSettings is a PowerShell Module to help you securely keep settings information, like API access keys.
# You use the Add-SecureSetting command to a new secure setting.

# You can store a string:
Add-SecureSetting AStringSetting 'A String' 

# You can store a secure string, which you can ask for with Read-Host -AsSecureString
Add-SecureSetting ASecureStringSetting (Read-Host "Is It Secret?" -AsSecureString)

# You can store a credential, which you can use for access to remote machines.   Prompt for credentials with Get-Credential.
Add-SecureSetting ACredentialSetting (Get-Credential)

# You can even store a complex hashtable (only if it contains strings, numbers, booleans, script blocks, and hashtables)
Add-SecureSetting AHashtableSetting @{
    a='b'
    c='d'
}

# Get-SecureSetting will list settings 
Get-SecureSetting 

# Get-SecureSetting can also list a single one AStringSetting
Get-SecureSetting AStringSetting

# Get-SecureSetting will return results encrypted by default. If you need to access an encrypted result, use -Decrypted
Get-SecureSetting AStringSetting -Decrypted

# Get-SecureSetting -ValueOnly will return just the decrypted value, without an object containing it
Get-SecureSetting AStringSetting -ValueOnly

# Remove-SecureSetting will remove a secure setting.  It supports -WhatIf and -Confirm
Get-SecureSetting | Remove-SecureSetting -WhatIf

# This will clear all settings and prompt.  To avoid the prompt, use -Confirm:$false
Get-SecureSetting | Remove-SecureSetting  

# In a Pipeworks manifest, the SecureSetting list details the names of secured settings that will be pulled into the site:
New-PipeworksManifest -Name AManifest -SecureSetting AzurestorageAccountName, AzureStorageAccountKey

# When you use Get-SecureSetting inside of a webpage, it looks for settings in the web.config file.  
# If you write your functions to use -ValueOnly, you can have the script work the same in the console as it does on the web.
$storageAccount = Get-SecureSetting 'AzureStorageAccountName' -ValueOnly





 


